Vaishali Pramod Fulzele

Email id: aushreefulzele@gmail.com

Mobile: 8080897287

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am hard-working engineering graduate specialized in Computer Science Engineering from Rajiv Gandhi Engineering College Nagpur and did three years diploma specialized in Computer Science & Technology from Shree Datta Meghe Polytechnic Nagpur. I Worked in Email and chat process for US & Canadian clients. Recently I have completed She Arise Training that is provided by CSR Initiative of Altran, the part of Capgemini Governed by NASSCOM Foundation Under Centum Foundation. During this training Explores advanced Java topics and front-end skills with a focus on process of creating an application on how to develop Desktop application.

EDUCATION QUALIFICATIONS

Qualification	Institute	Year	SGPA/10/PER
B.E	Rajiv Gandhi College of Engineering & Research Nagpur	2022	7.9
DIPLOMA	Shree Datta Meghe Polytechnic Nagpur	2019	60.88%
HSC	Baba Nanak Sindhi Hindi High School & Jr College	2016	54.46%
SSC	Baba Nanak Sindhi Hindi High School & Jr College	2014	67.60%

TECHNICAL QUALIFICATIONS

Programming: JAVA, C, C++, MYSQL.

Platform: Windows, Vs code, Eclipse, MYSQL, GitHub, Ms Office

Web: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, WordPress



PROJECT

TITLE: ADVANCE DIGITAL VOICE ASSISTANT USING AI

Description: In this project we Collecting human voice from the mic, and convert voice into text using speech recognition library where speech recognition uses an Gaussian Mixture Model (GMM) algorithm and explore how this information could be used to improve the user experience for doing their operations using voice.

Technologies Used: python, HTML, CSS power point presentation skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Designation: Executive Email Support

Organization: Valethi Technologies Full Time

Duration: April 2023 - July 2023

INTERNSHIPS

Cojag Smart Technology Pvt. Ltd (Duration February 2022 - March 2022)

Description: As a Part of this Web Development Internship, I have learned to create a website using HTML, CSS, PHP, and Python

Skills: HTML, CSS, PHP, Python.

COURSES

Centum Foundation She Arise 2.0 Program.

(Duration October 2022-February 2023)

Description: As a part of this Full Stack Java Development Program, I have learned to work on Front-end as well as back-end skills

Skills: JDBC, JPA+ HIBERNET, MYSQL, JAVA.

CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Participated in LUMINESCENCE a national level model making competition 2k18.
- Attended Virtual Workshop regarding Front End Development in Centum Foundation She arise 2.0 program.

PERSONAL TRAITS

- Assertive.
- Adaptable.
- Driven and determined.
- Self-Motivated.

PERSONAL PROFILE

Name : Vaishali P. Fulzele
Date of birth : May 15, 1999
Father's name : Pramod D. Fulzele

Gender : FemaleNationality : Indian

• Linguistic Abilities : English, Hindi, Marathi

Place: Nagpur